  <query xmlns:yahoo="http://www.yahooapis.com/v1/base.rng" yahoo:count="15" yahoo:created="2010-05-06T04:11:20Z" yahoo:lang="en-US">
      <results>
          <item>
              <title>Ahmadinejad: Osama bin Laden not in Iran, more likely in D.C.</title>
              <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 19:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/21825a991b879698a3d9195ef98f2d53#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://www.roguegovernment.com/index.php?news_id=21021</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/21825a991b879698a3d9195ef98f2d53</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/21825a991b879698a3d9195ef98f2d53</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Osama bin Laden may be the most wanted man on the planet, but Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad said he has an idea where the terrorist leader is holed up: not a damp cave in the Middle East, but some far cozier setting in Washington, D.C. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Iran&amp;#039;s president quips that the terrorist leader is holed up in Washington, D.C.The apparently sarcastic quip came during an interview with ABC News&amp;#039; George Stephanopoulos as Ahmadinejad responded to a claim in new documentary &amp;quot;Feathered Cocaine&amp;quot; that bin Laden has been living comfortably in Tehran, Iran, for years.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Jewish media plays down pro-illegal immigration thugs who terrorized Santa Cruz</title>
              <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 02:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/a1c876e8383e9fb73c80b59d474d60d6#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://www.prisonplanet.com/pro-illegal-immigration-thugs-terrorize-santa-cruz-corporate-media-shrugs.html</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/a1c876e8383e9fb73c80b59d474d60d6</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/a1c876e8383e9fb73c80b59d474d60d6</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>&#x201c;A large group of protesters demonstrating at a May Day rally for worker&#x2019;s and immigrant rights downtown broke off into a riot vandalizing about a dozen businesses around 10:30 p.m. Saturday, police said,&#x201d; reports The Santa Cruz Sentinel.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
An Associated Press report states that eighteen businesses were damaged as pro-immigrants rights activists engaged in violent riots, spraying graffiti, smashing windows, setting fire to shop fronts, and causing damage to a cost of up to $100,000 dollars.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&#x201c;The damage that was caused was without purpose,&#x201d; Capt. Steve Clark said. &#x201c;It was senseless violence that victimized a community who cannot afford to be victimized in this manner. This did nothing to add credit to whatever they believed their cause was.&#x201d;</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Officials: NY bomber confesses in terrorism plot</title>
              <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 02:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/58f75d84ceb026b3096d8c2616fbdb0b#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://rawstory.com/news/afp/NY_bomber_confesses_in_terrorism_pl_05042010.html</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/58f75d84ceb026b3096d8c2616fbdb0b</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/58f75d84ceb026b3096d8c2616fbdb0b</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>A Pakistani-American man arrested as he tried to flee the country has confessed to the failed bomb in New York&amp;#039;s Times Square and will be charged with international terrorism, US officials said Tuesday.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Faisal Shahzad had &amp;quot;provided valuable intelligence and evidence&amp;quot; to interrogators,&amp;quot; said FBI Director John Pistole.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Officials suggest the plot, initially believed by analysts to resemble a &amp;quot;lone-wolf&amp;quot; attack, in fact stretched all the way to Pakistan, where Shahzad, a naturalized US citizen, was born.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In Karachi, security officials said they had detained two people based on telephone records connecting them to Shahzad. An official, speaking on condition of anonymity, said the pair were related to the New York suspect.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Shahzad will be charged with &amp;quot;an act of terrorism transcending national borders, attempted use of a weapon of mass destruction,&amp;quot; Attorney General Eric Holder said.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Did the Kent State massacres have to happen?</title>
              <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 02:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/3eb18c185ded588f67a54f14cac85040#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://consortiumnews.com/2010/050410.html</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/3eb18c185ded588f67a54f14cac85040</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/3eb18c185ded588f67a54f14cac85040</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Forty years ago, the United States took a very ugly turn as President Richard Nixon escalated the war in Indochina by invading Cambodia, prompting angry college protests, including a confrontation at Kent State which ended with National Guardsmen killing four students on May 4, 1970. &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
With Nixon denouncing protesters as &amp;quot;bums,&amp;quot; the President&amp;#039;s &#x201c;silent majority&#x201d; was pitted against an increasingly radicalized anti-war movement. Parents turned against their own children, and &#x201c;hardhats&#x201d; spat on &#x201c;hippies.&#x201d; Fissures opened in U.S. society that have never entirely closed.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Today, looking at the consequences from the resulting Republican political dominance over much of the past four decades &#x2013; weakened labor unions, rampant deregulation, a shrinking American middle class, a swelling national debt, endless foreign wars, crimped civil liberties, and a deeply polarized electorate &#x2013; the question must be: did it all have to happen?</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Ahmadinejad speaks at the UN nuclear conference</title>
              <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 01:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/04b5be2f679479acd2d758a76ecedc40#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://www.politicaltheatrics.net/2010/05/ahmadinejad-speaks-at-the-un-nuclear-conference/</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/04b5be2f679479acd2d758a76ecedc40</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/04b5be2f679479acd2d758a76ecedc40</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Remember the following facts:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Israel has nuclear weapons, it refuses to be a signatory to the NNPT, or have its nuclear sites inspected by the IAEA.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Iran has no nuclear weapons, is a signatory of the NNPT and allows IAEA inspections.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Israel has nuclear weapons,Iran does not. Israel will not sign the NNPT,Iran has signed it. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Who&#x2019;s the &#x2018;bad guy&#x2019; here again?</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Is Pakistan the next evil doer?</title>
              <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 01:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/fc01db60271783024ae9141418ae203b#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://mycatbirdseat.com/2010/05/jeff-gates-is-pakistan-the-next-evil-doer/</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/fc01db60271783024ae9141418ae203b</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/fc01db60271783024ae9141418ae203b</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Who better than the &#x201c;Taliban of Pakistan&#x201d; to advance the 911 narrative? The Taliban is Evil. Pakistan is Muslim. Therefore&#x2026;.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Who was surprised to find Pakistan associated with a &#x201c;significant terrorist event&#x201d; in New York? Was anyone surprised that this &#x201c;car bomb&#x201d; incident occurred in the same city as the last significant event? Or that news reports promptly featured the Taliban of Pakistan?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Who labeled it a significant terrorist event?  A &#x201c;security analyst&#x201d; with IntelCenter.  Visit the site and remember the old adage: Best Story Wins.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Was this a genuine terrorist event? Or was this an agent provocateur operation meant to freshen up a stale storyline: the Global War on Terrorism?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Remember the &#x201c;Christmas Day Bomber&#x201d;? Were you surprised to find that &#x201c;significant terrorist event&#x201d; was an Israeli operation? Or have you not yet realized its source? See Christmas Day Crotch Bomber Tied to Israel, FBI</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Times Square bomb hoax, Israeli intel group SITE shows its hand</title>
              <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 01:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/cd5a7d7a9e71e8a1829a9b697ade6d94#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://www.veteranstoday.com/2010/05/02/gordon-duff-time-square-bomb-hoax-israeli-intel-group-shows-its-hand/</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/cd5a7d7a9e71e8a1829a9b697ade6d94</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/cd5a7d7a9e71e8a1829a9b697ade6d94</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Who would have believed it?  Only days after a warning of an Israeli &#x201c;false flag&#x201d; bombing against the US &#x201c;in the works&#x201d; a massive car bomb is discovered in Time Square!  Better yet, though no intelligence organization in the world could discover anyone claiming responsibility for this embarrassing failure, SITE Intelligence, a group rumored as the &#x201c;voice of the Mossad&#x201d; has placed the blame on the Pakistani Taliban.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This is the same group that has come up with numerous bin Laden &#x201c;audio&#x201d; tapes, seemingly, though tiny and nearly totally unstaffed, whenever it is convenient for Israel to point a finger at someone, magically Site Intelligence, run by former IDF soldier Rita Katz, whose father was executed as a spy by Saddam Hussein, makes another &#x201c;unbelievable&#x201d; intelligence find.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Site Intelligence finds are not only timely for Israel but always tend to support mysterious organizations run from the caves of the Afghanistan/Pakistan border region.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Shocking: Max Blumenthal exposes Jewish extremist&apos;s rally in NYC</title>
              <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 17:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/25943730822f3d0b5f8108ae1fef3277#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://www.informationclearinghouse.info/article25354.htm</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/25943730822f3d0b5f8108ae1fef3277</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/25943730822f3d0b5f8108ae1fef3277</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>The Manhattan rally took on a distinctively Tea Party-flavor. Besides issuing maximalist calls for the expulsion of the Palestinians, demonstrators assailed Obama as a secret Muslim with no legitimate right to serve as President of the United States. When I was identified by a particularly ornery rally participant as &#x201c;the self-hating asshole Max Blumenthal,&#x201d; I decided it was time to make my exit.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
However, as I walked down 44th Street towards the subway, an elderly man grabbed me and attempted to snatch my camera (I had seen the gun-toting Marzel use similar tactics on anti-settlement activists documenting his exploits in the West Bank). &#x201c;You&#x2019;re not a Jew! Give me the film!&#x201d; the man exclaimed. A mob of demonstrators suddenly formed and began advancing towards me. Luckily, two NYPD officers were nearby. They pried the man off me and gave me enough time to escape.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Who controls the US Treasury Department?</title>
              <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 21:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/1ef65fc9e529b23e8c68ac3e08a14c65#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://theinfounderground.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=7&amp;t=10912</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/1ef65fc9e529b23e8c68ac3e08a14c65</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/1ef65fc9e529b23e8c68ac3e08a14c65</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Of the twenty top officials in the U.S. Treasury Department, twelve are Jews. This is a numerical representation of 60%. Jews are approximately 2% of the United States population.* This means that Jews are over-represented among the top officials of the U.S. Treasury Department by a factor of 30 times times, or 3,000 percent. This extreme numerical over-representation of Jews among the top officials of the U.S. Treasury Department cannot be explained away as a coincidence or as the result of mere random chance. You must ask yourself how such an incredibly small and extremely unrepresentative minority ethnic group that only represents 2% of the American population could so completely dominate the highest levels of the U.S. Treasury Department.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Fed Reserve Chairman admits to printing $1.3 Trillion out of thin air</title>
              <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 21:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/186de1e9931d1110146fba23007c498b#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://usawatchdog.com/bernanke-admits-printing-1-3-trillion-out-of-thin-air/</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/186de1e9931d1110146fba23007c498b</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/186de1e9931d1110146fba23007c498b</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Fed Chairman Ben Bernanke admitted the central bank created $1.3 trillion out of thin air to buy mortgage backed securities.  This shocking admission came from the Joint Economic Committee hearing on Capital Hill last week.  I was dumbfounded when I saw Bernanke shake his head in the affirmative as Representative Ron Paul said, &#x201c;Well, where did you get the money? You created this money. So you did monetize debt, and that went into the banking system.&#x201d;  I was amazed he admitted this.  I looked up the original hearing on C-Span to make sure the clip was not edited.  It was not.   &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
What is even more shocking is I could not find a single mainstream news agency that covered this revelation.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Who controls the Federal Reserve?</title>
              <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 19:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/852c9141047be10428818d358eafd4e3#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://theinfounderground.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=7&amp;t=10911</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/852c9141047be10428818d358eafd4e3</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/852c9141047be10428818d358eafd4e3</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>For the past forty years, every Chairman of the Federal Reserve System has been a Jew, except for a brief period of seventeen months. Here are the Chairmen of the Federal Reserve System since 1970.&lt;br /&gt;
Jews are approximately 2% of the United States population.* The probability that almost every Chairman of the Federal Reserve System since 1970 would be a Jew is infinitly small. This extreme numerical over-representation of Jews among the Chairmen of the Federal Reserve System cannot be explained away as a coincidence or as the result of mere random chance. You must ask yourself how such an incredibly small and extremely unrepresentative minority ethnic group that only represents 2% of the American population could so dominate the chairmanship of the Federal Reserve System.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Who controls the Bilderberg Group?</title>
              <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/87f1224f35fc787d7b989b2df2225ed2#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://theinfounderground.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=7&amp;t=10903</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/87f1224f35fc787d7b989b2df2225ed2</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/87f1224f35fc787d7b989b2df2225ed2</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Of the twenty-six Americans who attended the 2009 Bilderberg conference, eighteen are Jews. This is a numerical representation of 69%. Jews are approximately 2% of the United States population. This means that Jews are over-represented among the American attendees of the 2009 Bilderberg conference by a factor of 34.5 times, or 3,450 percent. This extreme numerical over-representation of Jews among the American attendees of the 2009 Bilderberg conference cannot be explained away as a coincidence or as the result of mere random chance. You must ask yourself how such an incredibly small and extremely unrepresentative minority ethnic group that only represents 2% of the United States population could so dominate this important and influential international conference.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Another Israeli scam: Darfur aid dollars funding West Bank settlements</title>
              <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 03:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/3e61c8fcbd47607322d58b96e0ef90fb#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://onlinejournal.com/artman/publish/article_5708.shtml</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/3e61c8fcbd47607322d58b96e0ef90fb</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/3e61c8fcbd47607322d58b96e0ef90fb</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>Persons working with aid organizations assisting the victims of the Darfur conflict have passed on the news that they have confirmed through their contacts in the so called &amp;quot;Save Darfur Coalition&amp;quot; that millions of dollars raised to help the Darfur refugees have ended up in Israeli bank accounts. These accounts help fund programs that include illegal Israeli settlements in the occupied West Bank. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The Darfur funds were diverted to Israel by either co-mingling the funds with those used to support the Israeli projects or through a more complex system of grants to other &amp;quot;aid&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;relief&amp;quot; organizations that allowed the eventual destination of the funds to be almost impossible to trace.</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>Remembering the OKC Bombing</title>
              <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 03:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/d84b09dbebda8eea417fb96e2e3d0c28#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://adap2k.blogspot.com/2010/04/remembering-okc-bombing-12160org-topic.html</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/d84b09dbebda8eea417fb96e2e3d0c28</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/d84b09dbebda8eea417fb96e2e3d0c28</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>A collection of articles spotlighting the OKC Bombing courtesy of the 12.160 Social Network</description>
          </item>
          <item>
              <title>CBS Breaking News WTC 7 Collapse first reports &quot;Don&apos;t know if it was demolition experts&quot;</title>
              <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 02:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
              <guid isPermaLink="false">http://delicious.com/url/5d93f941961e10ef9b88536157efc88d#maasanova</guid>
              <link>http://kennysideshow.blogspot.com/2010/04/911-cbs-breaking-news-wtc7-collapse.html</link>
              <dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">maasanova</dc:creator>
              <comments>http://delicious.com/url/5d93f941961e10ef9b88536157efc88d</comments>
              <wfw:commentRss xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/url/5d93f941961e10ef9b88536157efc88d</wfw:commentRss>
              <source url="http://feeds.delicious.com/v2/rss/maasanova">maasanova&apos;s bookmarks</source>
              <description>CBS Breaking News WTC 7 Collapse first reports &amp;quot;Don&amp;#039;t know if it was demolition experts&amp;quot;</description>
          </item>
      </results>
  </query>

